Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/nguy3n47 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

NextJS

Unit Testing

Git

Certifications

JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures

Software Engineer

Node.js (Intermediate)

Rest API (Intermediate)

JavaScript (Intermediate)

Honors-Awards

Scholarship from ScrumViet

Collaborator - Vietnam Web Summit 2019

Nguyen Vu

Software Engineer @ CloudVerse

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

I'm a Software Engineer with 3.5+ years of experience in Web Development. Interested in devising a better problem-solving method for challenging tasks and learning new trending technologies and frameworks. I am looking for a new challenge to improve myself as well as to become a better engineer.

Experience

CloudVerse.Al Software Engineer January 2024 - Present (1 year 3 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

NAB

Software Engineer June 2023 - October 2023 (5 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

LASTMILE WORKS Co., Ltd.

Software Engineer

October 2022 - October 2023 (1 year 1 month)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Vinova Pte. Ltd. Software Engineer October 2021 - September 2022 (1 year) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Education

VNUHCM - University of Science
Bachelor's degree, Computer Software Engineering (2018 - 2022)